(Space Rice Cake)
(We're beginning the first business day in Seoul.)
(The launch of the new menu item is going smoothly.)
(The kitchen team has great teamwork.)
(You're Table 5, right?)
Our food didn't come out.
(But the Seoul branch is still new to them.)
(Please give me a moment.)
(Using a kiosk is so difficult for me.)
(The service team starts to make mistakes.)
(They have so much work to do.)
(And they feel rushed.)
(The dinner rush is already about to start.)
(Just wait and see what our new part-timer is in for.)
(The Earth Arcaders are exhausted and want extra hands.)
(They're just waiting for the new recruit to join them.)
It's 5:30pm now.
I'll turn the sign to "open."
- Okay.
- Yes.
Yes, Your Majesty.
All right. Let's go.
(Current time, 5:30pm)
Space Rice Cake...
is now open for dinner!
Okay. Let's go.
(The members cheerfully start working in the kitchen.)
The rice cakes are just incredible today.
- What is that?
- They're just incredible.
(The rice cake buns are looking extra tasty today.)
(The dessert team also works hard to serve customers.)
Move the less standout ones to the middle.
(Roaming around)
(There's no one coming toward the restaurant.)
Don't we have any customers yet?
There's a table booked for 5:30pm, though.
- Why haven't they come yet?
- They must be running late...
They must be stuck in traffic.
Why haven't they come yet? They need to arrive on time...
so we can serve the food fresh.
- She prepared the buns.
- I prepared them...
so we can get two burgers out the door immediately.
- Dinner...
- That's just the way business is.
When you're fully prepared, no one shows up.
- My point exactly.
- When you slack off on the prep,
you get slammed with customers.
You just can't predict it.
(Just when they thought business was unpredictable...)
That's what business is like.
That's so true.
(The long-awaited customers finally arrived.)
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Hello.
Please come on in.
I'm nervous.
(The arrival of the customers freezes the chefs.)
One Too much rice cake in a burger Beef slid in combo,
- One tteokbokki.
- one tteokbokki...
You can upgrade the combo drink to an ade.
There is an additional charge of 50 cents for that.
And you'll be served an ade instead of Coke.
Then we'll upgrade the drink and order one ade.
Excellent. That makes two ades in total.
- Yes.
- We'll serve you two ades.
Please take your time looking at the menu.
Shrimp...
Can I change it to an ade, please?
Please give me a second.
I'll upgrade your combo drink to an ade.
Can I also get a carrot cake, please?
The pop-up store is open as well.
We can't sell any products, though.
Here you go. Thank you.
Please put this on your table.
(She perfectly handled the order, including the table number.)
We got an order for Table One.
The burger will go out first.
(The kitchen gets to work right away.)
Be careful.
(First, she melts some butter to cook the patty.)
(Then, she places the thick patty onto the buttered griddle.)
(After pressing it flat with a spatula,)
(she grills the patty until it's golden brown.)
It's so big.
(Meanwhile, she preps rice cakes for tteokbokki.)
(In goes the garaetteok.)
(She's working steadily, showing the qualities of a head chef.)
(It's like a relay race between Seoul and Goheung.)
There's no question about my tteokbokki.
(There's no question about the original tteokbokki.)
You're the problem.
- I'm putting it on.
- That looks crazy good.
(The dazzling steam show)
- I like that sound.
- That's so cool.
I really like that sound.
I'm all about putting on a cooking show.
(The cheese and the beef patty have finally become one.)
(Meanwhile, our sous chef...)
(puts the tteoksagna in the oven first.)
(She has even finished prepping the shrimp patty.)
I think the tteokbokki and burger can go out at the same time.
Yes, chef.
- Oh, we got an order...
- Okay. That's done.
for Do you like mint? Of carrot! Cake.
The carrot cake I'm best at making
(She's even improvising a song as she starts making it.)
I'll make it in advance, I'll make it in advance
I'll make it in advance
So that we can help each other
(The lyrics encourage labour quite heavily.)
(She puts a spoonful of yuzu marmalade in the cup.)
- This will go out in five minutes.
- Okay.
(And then she dances for a bit.)
(The end)
(She places gijeongtteok on top of the yuzu marmalade.)
- And then...
- I made it.
(Next up is the mint cream.)
I feel like I'm both Ma Bok Rim and Ma Bok Pal.
I feel like I'm a butcher's shop owner.
My goodness. Gosh.
- What's wrong?
- It burst.
Oh, my gosh.
(The piping bag burst at the top.)
Greed for finishing everything at once...
always leads to a disaster like this.
(This time, she calmly makes it one step at a time.)
(It's finally ready.)
(Proud of herself)
You're so cute.
(Chuckling)
She was completely focused, standing next to me...
I'm the carrot expert.
- I'm like Torong.
- You're like Torong.
The tteokbokki is ready.
The burger is ready.
We're serving the burger and tteokbokki together.
That was incredibly fast.
I'll erase them for you.
- That was too easy.
- Exactly.
My goodness. Exactly.
Here's your food.
Here's the tteoksagna. It's very hot.
Okay.
- We...
- This is the best day of my life.
Sorry?
This is the best day of my life.
(Touched)
She watches "Earth Arcade" every day.
I'm deeply moved.
It's been a long day.
(It feels like her tiredness melts away.)
I'm deeply moved.
Where did you come from?
- Yeonsinnae.
- Gupabal...
- You came from Yeonsinnae?
- Yes.
(The child customer came from Yeonsinnae.)
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
(Sniffing)
(Whimpering)
(She tries to hold back tears, but she bursts into tears.)
- What's that noise?
- What's wrong?
A child customer told me,
"This is the best day of my life."
She told me those exact words.
(Wailing)
- That was so touching.
- It really is.
- "This is the best day of my life."
- That's so touching.
Really?
- I'm jealous.
- Does she like the food?
She didn't tell me that...
(Excuse me?)
(She killed the mood instantly.)
- I was deeply moved.
- It's touching.
- She just killed the mood.
- I killed...
I mean, they paid for the food.
(A feeling of being touched is a luxury in my kitchen.)
She's a customer too, after all.
(The little customers are trying the burger.)
- The rice cake is good.
- Is it?
(Chef Lee, she says it's good.)
The rice cake is so tasty.
(The food is this tasty, but...)
(The dining area is nearly empty.)
This is insane. Why is it so quiet?
- Exactly. Why...
- It's like a calm before the storm.
Why won't anyone come?
The work is too easy today.
Man, business is so slow.
(But so many people checked out the place online.)
We got 5,000 saves on CatchTable, but where is everyone?
(Forget 5,000 people. There aren't even 5 people here.)
Did a competitor just open up right next door?
(Giggling)
- Did a competitor just open up?
- That might be the case.
Ma'am, please calm down a bit.
We need to make money. What are you doing?
It's not like that.
Please calm down a bit, ma'am.
- How can I calm down right now?
- Pardon?
We had 5,000 people on CatchTable trying to book a table. How...
But things are so slow. Look at all these pots I prepped.
(She prepped so many pots.)
- When you're fully prepared, - Exactly.
- you don't get slammed.
- Is this normal?
But we take reservations through CatchTable.
I think people will come a bit later since it's Sunday evening.
- Let me read you the new review.
- Yes, please.
- This customer gave us five stars.
- Oh, nice.
"The person who took our order was really cheerful."
"I'll never forget her."
- That must be Eun Ji.
- There's more.
"The lady with the twintails who waited tables..."
"was so pretty. She could be an idol."
- That's great.
- This customer is so sharp.
"It was fun because the cooks were full of energy."
- "Can you..."
- No comments about the food.
"Can you extend it for a few more days?" That's it.
We really are full of energy. That's all we've got.
(Holding a grudge)
- Are we not?
- My point exactly.
Right.
It's so peaceful, just like a calm before the storm.
(A mysterious vehicle is approaching the restaurant.)
"Could I order, please?"
"I'd like to order, please."
Is this it?
(Someone arrives in front of the restaurant.)
Goodness. I'm nervous.
(With excitement and tension in the air...)
Look at that. It's so cute.
(Space Rice Cake, 2nd Earth branch)
- Could I order, please?
- Hello... Oh, my.
- Why?
- My goodness.
- What brings you here?
- I heard about your restaurant.
(Frozen)
What?
- Hello. What brings you here?
- Oh, my.
I heard about your restaurant.
What?
- Hey, taskmaster.
- Oh, hello.
- Part-timer, come over here.
- Hello.
- Hold on. You're so late.
- Come over here, part-timer.
- What took you so long, part-timer?
- I was so surprised to see her.
- Actually...
- Guys, she's a customer.
- Oh, I see. I'm very sorry.
- Oh, she's a customer?
- You're not a part-timer?
- Gosh, seriously.
- I see. She's a customer?
- I thought she was a part-timer.
- What should we do?
I'm so upset. I'm going to write a bad review online.
I'm very sorry.
- KARINA.
- I'll leave a bad review.
No wonder she looked...
- Are you going to pay for food?
- No, I'm here to help you out.
- So she's a part-timer.
- She's a part-timer.
- Part-timer, come over here.
- Hey! Seriously.
- Part-timer, come with me.
- Come here.
Say hello to the camera.
- Hello.
- Say hello to the camera.
- You scared me.
- It's nice to meet you all.
(She's the leader of aespa, the icon of fierce charisma.)
(Her alter ego in the alternate universe is gentle and soft.)
(Today's part-timer, KARINA)
(She gives a formal greetings to everyone.)
Ms. Part-timer, if I may...
Have you ever worked part-time in a kitchen?
This is my first time.
- First time ever in my life.
- Have you ever waited tables?
- I've never done that before.
- You're so pretty. You're gorgeous.
She looks really beautiful today.
A part-timer shouldn't wear such heavy makeup.
I came here right after recording a music show.
- Really?
- That's amazing.
- Thank you so much for coming.
- I had to wear full makeup.
- I've never met her before. Hello.
- You're wearing gloves.
I'll put on a fresh pair. Hello. Oh, my.
Why did you hire such an expensive employee?
She's way too high-profile to be a part-timer here.
My point exactly. What should we do?
Oh, right. This is the restroom.
She's so pretty that I can't even look at her.
- You're prettier than her.
- Her proportions are insane.
You're prettier than KARINA.
Both you and KARINA are pretty,
- but you're prettier in my eyes.
- Then that's all that matters.
She looks smart.
- Right. I'm sure...
- I think she'll do well.
- Hold on.
- KARINA must be sharp at work.
(She's changed her clothes!)
Oh, my. You look great in it.
- She has to look pretty.
- She looks great in it.
- She looks so cute.
- My, she looks gorgeous.
- It looks perfect on you.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- You look so pretty.
- Should she...
- Should she wait tables?
- Thank you.
- She's...
- I'm the taskmaster here, KARINA.
- You're the taskmaster here?
- As the service team taskmaster,
- give her a tour of the place.
- The youngest... Show her around.
- Before that, how do I look today?
- You look really cute.
- Thank you. Let's go.
- "Thank you."
- You look so pretty today.
- It was the right answer, right?
- I could've been in trouble, right?
- You look so pretty.
- So you came right after the shoot?
- You look cute.
- Yes, I did.
- Thank you, KARINA.
(My pleasure)
- Ma'am. I mean, part-timer.
- Yes?
- Yu Jin. Oh, my. It's a mortar.
- This is...
- a high-angle photo booth.
- Where...
- You can take mirror selfies here.
- Posing like this?
Yes, that's what this place is for.
(Posing together)
- Hold on a second. Hey, ladies.
- Yes?
Come down here.
- Walk her through the menu.
- Oh, right.
- Okay.
- Come over here.
- You run a tight ship around here.
- We have strict discipline.
- Part-timer, have a seat.
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right.
- Explain how the ade upgrade works.
- Too much rice cake... Eun Ji.
- "Too much rice cake..."
- Yes?
- Can you show me just once?
How do we describe the beef burger?
When you say this name, you should say it with a melody.
- Let's say Yu Jin is a customer.
- What's "Too much rice cake?"
Too much rice cake in a burger
That's not all.
- Patty slid in - KARINA.
It sounds like a lie, right?
- But they actually do that.
- You're lying.
- They really do that.
- Don't be territorial.
- It's true.
- Guess what they did before.
Chestnut Tyranno
- It's true.
- She thinks we're lying.
Chestnut Tyranno
It's true.
- You're lying. Are you serious?
- It's true.
- Oh, hello.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- This new part-timer started today.
- Welcome.
Could I please get the name for your CatchTable reservation?
We also have a shrimp burger combo.
- The combo comes with a soda.
- I see.
- And we have this ade...
- Too much rice cake in a burger
- Patty slid in - We actually do that.
- You're lying.
- We really do it.
- There's a task for you.
- Okay.
- You'll get used to it in no time.
- Right. Don't I get an apron?
- Oh, right.
- Right. She needs an apron.
- She's incredibly beautiful.
- Indeed.
Part-timer, put it on by yourself.
- She looks so pretty today.
- She looks so pretty.
- Regardless of her age...
- She agreed, feeling helpless.
(Yu Jin failed to discipline KARINA.)
I'm too scared to work here.
Part-timer, hurry up. Finish it in five seconds.
- Five, four...
- Help me just this once.
- Help her.
- Okay.
(Meanwhile, outside the kitchen...)
Oh, my. You are not a party of four.
- Right. I'm expecting next month.
- That's right.
(Hi, baby.)
Say hi to her, Shutddang.
Shutddang.
Shutddang, I love you so much.
- Do you think Shutddang heard me?
- Yes.
Wonderful.
Listen up.
(She returns proudly with the order sheet.)
- We got an order, chef.
- We must listen to the order.
- Honesty, humility, ahk.
- Humility, ahk.
- Hurry up and tell us.
- We must listen to the order.
One Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki,
- Answer.
- Congratulations.
- one shrimp burger combo, - Answer.
- Yes!
- one beef burger combo,
- one potato cream tteoksagna,
- Yes!
- and one mint carrot cake.
- They swapped the combo drinks...
for ades for both of the combos.
- We got an order!
- Yes!
- Can you read it out loud for them?
- Yes. We got an order.
All right. Put it on the board here.
- Table 4.
- It's for Table 4.
- Yes.
- What?
One Do you like mint? Of carrot! Cake,
one potato cream tteoksagna,
one Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki,
one Too much rice cake in a burger Plump shrimp pop combo,
and two Too much rice cake in a burger Beef slid in combos.
- Got it.
- Thank you.
(But there is a catch.)
What? The receipt only shows one shrimp burger combo.
What?
(They ordered 2 shrimp burger combos.)
We actually ordered two shrimp burger combos.
Oh, I see. Then...
Could I charge you...
- for the missing one separately?
- Sure.
- Here's your receipt. Thank you.
- Thank you.
We got an additional order. One additional shrimp burger.
- Got it.
- It's for Table Four.
- The original tteokbokki is ready.
- Got it.
(So the order sheet for Table 4 was split into 2.)
- Gosh. Come on.
- The original tteokbokki is ready.
(3 beef burgers, 3 shrimp burgers, 2 tteokbokki, 2 tteoksagna)
(2 carrot cake)
(6 pomegranate ades)
(The part-timer washes her hands first.)
Chestnut Tyranno
I'll give you nitrile gloves since you have small hands.
- Give her the extra small size.
- I'm touched.
(I'm touched, my senior Yu Jin.)
(She puts on the gloves handed to her by Senior An.)
Did you put them on?
Ms. Part-timer,
if you have some free time,
can you make four ades...
- as you did just earlier?
- Four ades?
I can absolutely do that.
- Give it a try.
- Got it.
We need to serve the original tteokbokki right away.
It'll be ready shortly.
Just give me two minutes.
(First, she takes out the cups for ades.)
(She puts in a generous amount of pomegranate syrup.)
Four spoonfuls of it. Yes.
You're doing great.
You must've worked at a restaurant before.
- You seem quite skillful.
- I'm doing well, right?
- People say I'm smart and thorough.
- You really are.
It smells so good.
(She goes heavy on the ice and sparkling water too.)
(Her refreshing smile is a bonus.)
(After mixing thoroughly...)
(and placing a sprig of rosemary)
(KARINA's first pomegranate ade is ready.)
After shooting a music show...
- It must be very exhausting.
- I know.
KARINA, could you stick in four straws?
- Oh, right. I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
KARINA, you're not allowed to apologize...
- in this kitchen.
- There's no need to be sorry.
Instead, we say, "I love you."
- I love you.
Could you put the burger together? I beg you.
Okay, I will.
I spilled some. Please clean it up.
(The chef doesn't have time for love right now.)
(Remaining Order Status)
(It's because she's been hit with a flood of orders.)
Eun Ji, there are four.
- Two, three, four.
- Okay.
(Pans of tteokbokki next to one another)
(Next to tteoksagna is...)
(another tteoksagna.)
- Please put these together.
- Okay.
(The endless road of hard work)
Let's do our best.
(Let's do our best...)
(Hall different animal)
(Slightly embarrassed)
(Animal in English)
(Animal in English is)
(That's enough.)
- Small original tteokbokki is done.
- Okay.
Young Ji, this looks really good.
Yes, it does.
- I'll take it off.
- Okay.
That sounds good.
- Do we go together?
- Yes, you should go together.
(The part-timer serves for the first time.)
Okay, take your time.
We're not in a hurry.
We have CatchTable, so there's no need to hurry.
(Being cautious)
The work became so much easier.
- Be careful.
- Gosh, this isn't easy.
- These are the stairs to paradise.
- Seriously.
(The part-timer starts to serve.)
We can't ask the customers to come down, right?
- Of course not.
- Okay.
The pomegranate ades are for Table Four.
- The rest is for Table 3.
- For Table 3?
Yes.
- Is that for us?
- Here are your ades first.
Okay.
- You're very beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your food.
My goodness.
(Blooming with smiles)
- Hello.
- Who ordered the beef burger?
Could you put it here?
- Gosh.
- Please be careful.
Our child is completely stunned...
- from seeing you.
- Get a hold of yourself.
She's completely stunned.
(While the part-timer is showing off her presence)
This is the beef burger.
(The service master keeps serving.)
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
- Seriously...
Did you order a shrimp burger?
Yes, I ordered a shrimp burger.
Me too. These two ordered a beef burger.
We can cut them in half and share them.
Sure.
One shrimp burger and one beef burger are ready.
- Okay.
We served everything for Table Four.
- We're doing very well so far.
(A carrot cake remains, but the original order is discarded.)
- A shrimp burger...
- It's for Table Four.
I'll serve both of them.
(Table 4 additional order, 1 shrimp burger combo)
Let me give you the pickles.
Did Table 4 order 1 shrimp and 1 beef burger?
- Yes.
- Thank you for your generous order.
- Here's your shrimp burger.
- That's for me.
Here you go.
- One beef burger.
- Yes.
Is this everything you ordered?
We're waiting for one more shrimp burger.
One more shrimp burger?
One more shrimp burger and a cake.
- That's for later.
- A carrot cake?
- All right.
- Thank you.
Sure.
(She returns to the kitchen while feeling uneasy.)
Friends, one shrimp burger is missing at Table Four.
Why is it missing?
(To see what went wrong, she looks at the order.)
- Did they order two?
- One shrimp burger was served...
to Table Four.
We served the first one just now.
- Take a look.
- What happened exactly?
Table 4 ordered 2 shrimp burgers.
- Did they order 2?
- But only 1 was served.
Seriously?
Table 4 ordered 1.
- They ordered another one later.
- An extra?
We have an extra order of shrimp burger.
- Okay.
It's for Table Four.
I'll fry it.
Okay.
(There's one more thing that they forgot.)
(The missing carrot cake wasn't even communicated.)
Could you place some rosemary on the pomegranate ades?
(Just then, customers come out after finishing their meal.)
KARINA, let's go and clean up together.
(Following the service master up to the 2nd floor)
Isn't working part-time exhausting?
(It feels even more exhausting today.)
Grab one of these from here.
This is too small. Let's switch to this.
- Right?
- Yes.
- A bigger one is better.
- You're right.
(Grabbing the dishcloths)
Are you wearing an apron?
Why don't you slip this in here like me?
My gosh, it feels like I'm working part-time.
(It's because you're working part-time.)
I try to enjoy work.
(They're off to start cleaning.)
KARINA, everyone at this table left.
- It looks like they enjoyed it.
- They really enjoyed the food.
They didn't leave any food.
It's so rewarding.
(Feeling rewarded from seeing empty dishes)
(Cleaning up thoroughly while thinking of next customers)
Gosh, this is brutal.
(A groan echoes through the hall.)
Goodness, my back.
My back.
(Please let me go home.)
- You have to go downstairs.
- Okay.
Shall I start the dishes right away?
I'd appreciate that, KARINA.
Yu Jin, could you help with this?
(The part-timer's next mission: Washing dishes)
(Putting on the rubber gloves first)
Are you washing the dishes?
Yes, I'll start it now.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry about making you do the dishes.
Let's kiss.
- No way.
- She likes to kiss.
That's so harsh.
(Getting turned down is part of her everyday life.)
(About to properly tackle the dishes)
(A mountain of dishes)
I can't find the sponge.
Has anyone seen the sponge? Here it is.
(She found it buried in the mountain of dishes.)
(And so began her time with the dishes.)
(Washing the dishes in silence)
(Laughing)
- They didn't leave much behind.
- KARINA is...
also working away without saying a word.
- I know.
- She's taking it very seriously.
KARINA, that's what happens...
- when you're here.
- You're right.
It's so sad. An untouched ade that almost made it out.
(The part-timer's warmth still lingers in the ade.)
(While the part-timer is trapped in the endless cycle of dishwashing,)
(the next customers walk in.)
(A frightening stream of customers comes pouring in.)
This is our menu.
Take your time to look at it.
We have an order.
- Where's the tteoksagna?
- Here it is.
Please give me one tteoksagna first.
Okay.
KARINA, are you okay?
- Me?
- Yes.
I'm okay.
You look so lonely from the back.
That's true.
- Cooking can be...
- Right.
(Her back looks especially lonely.)
It can be lonely.
(And here's another lonely place.)
(Remaining order at Table 4, 1 shrimp burger combo)
(1 mint carrot cake)
Which one do you like the best?
- The shrimp burger.
- Me too.
The shrimp burger? Among these?
(The shrimp burger tastes especially good today.)
I want a shrimp burger too.
(A modest wish)
It hasn't come yet, right?
Eun Ji, here's one shrimp burger.
It's going to Table Five.
(She forgot about the missing order due to so much work.)
(Swoosh)
The food for our perfect Romeo and Juliet has arrived.
But Romeo and Juliet were a tragic couple, so I'll change it.
- You're Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin.
- Oh, my.
Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin of Yeonhui-dong.
I'm sorry.
I'm quite loud today.
- Here you go.
- You're so pretty.
Thank you.
I have no idea either.
(It's awkward to get angry about the missing shrimp order.)
- I'm sorry.
- Ask her.
Excuse me.
We haven't gotten one shrimp burger.
- A shrimp burger?
- Yes. And so...
(Going back through her memory)
(We need to get one more shrimp burger.)
(One shrimp burger and carrot cake)
- A carrot cake?
- Yes.
(A promise she made with them passes by.)
I'll go and check.
I'm sorry about that.
(She goes to the kitchen to share the news.)
Everyone, that time has come for us.
There has been a mistake.
At Table 4, 1 shrimp burger is missing...
and a carrot cake.
Okay, I'll hurry and make it.
It's not a mistake. It's almost ready.
That time has come for us too.
KARINA.
Could you bring me some arugula from the pantry...
and wash it for me?
Seeing you together feels like the worlds are colliding.
(Copying)
- I'll make the shrimp burger.
- KARINA.
Could you bring me a jar of yuzu marmalade?
- Yusanseul? Yuzu marmalade.
- Yuzu marmalade.
Arugula and...
Where is it? Here it is.
(She finds them fast with the skills used to find Black Mamba.)
You look like someone who's been working here for a few days.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You look like someone who's been working here for four days.
Can you give me one carrot cake?
Gosh, the mint cream.
(I've been flipped.)
- I got the order wrong.
- I see.
(For Do you like mint? Of carrot! Cake...)
(1. Yuzu marmalade)
(2. Gijeongtteok)
(3. Mint cream)
(The key is piling them in order.)
(But what Yu Jin made)
(Did mint go on top? Of carrot! Cake)
Please say that it's okay.
The beef is ready.
- Yu Jin, be careful.
- Okay.
- Don't get confused.
- Be careful.
We need to serve the missing order.
The shrimp burger is ready.
I'll make it faster than anyone.
I'll serve the carrot cake first.
Okay. I'm sorry about that.
Seven and eight for Table Four.
- I sincerely apologize.
- It's okay.
- There it is.
- It's very chaotic downstairs.
- I understand.
- I sincerely apologize about that.
We made it with extra love.
- I apologize about that.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry once again.
Can I get a small plate?
A small plate?
Actually, small plates are at the self-service station,
but I brought it for Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin...
of Yeonhui-dong.
- Thank you.
- They were available.
- Right. They were somewhere.
(The superstar couple couldn't find what was under their noses.)
(Meanwhile, KARINA of Yeonhui-dong)
Mimi, do you need all of this?
Just rinse it once...
and give it to me fast.
About this much?
Okay, I got it.
(The part-timer gets a new task.)
(Yu Jin is making another carrot cake.)
I got it wrong again. I must be out of my mind.
(Current Dessert Status, Did mint go on top?)
I must be out of my mind.
- What's wrong with me?
- It's okay.
Yu Jin, it's okay.
- Thank you. Mimi.
- It's really okay.
You're the best.
- Yu Jin, get a grip on yourself.
- Stay strong.
Mimi, I'm busy taking care of this.
Could you handle the potato puffs?
- Yes, they're in the fryer now.
- Thank you.
The floor is slippery, so be careful.
Okay.
(This time, she squeezes out a lot of mint cream first.)
The original tteokbokki is ready.
(Sprinkling sponge cake crumbs on top)
(Scraping the bottom very hard)
I'll bring you more ingredients.
Do you need sponge cake?
- Sponge cake is hard to find.
- I'll try to find it.
(The part-timer finds something to do on her own.)
Tell me now if you need anything.
Sponge cake...
Wait, you seem a little annoyed.
No, I'm not.
Sponge cake crumbs...
Crumbs should be somewhere around here.
There's sponge cake here.
Where are sponge cake crumbs?
(She only sees sponge cake.)
"Carrot."
(For the part-timer, this place is an escape room.)
They're not here.
(Meanwhile, Yu Jin is finishing up the carrot cake.)
(Carefully sticking in the shovel spoon)
One carrot cake is ready.
(Rushing)
Can I take this thing?
No one told me...
that I had to remove the plastic.
Are you kidding me?
- Should I take the whole thing?
- The whole thing?
No, take... Just take the whole thing.
- Going back and forth is annoying.
- It's okay.
I'm sorry.
- You're already busy, - It's okay.
but you got busier by coming here.
Put the sponge cake in the sieve...
- and crush it...
- Crush it?
- until it becomes fine like this.
- Okay.
Yu Jin, should I do this and put it over there?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(Additional task of making sponge cake crumbs)
- Goodbye.
- Eun Ji, a carrot cake is ready.
A carrot cake? Is it for Table Four?
Everything for Table Four is served now.
The beef will be ready in 20 seconds.
Okay.
For Table Seven...
You're making her lonely. Why isn't anyone answering?
I think I'm suited for this part-time job.
This is fun.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I have something to do tomorrow,
but I'm thinking of coming to your company dinner.
She's realistic. She's really going to come,
so she's talking realistically.
- I don't say things I don't mean.
- She doesn't.
That's scary.
I say things just to be nice, but she never does.
Exactly. When are you going to fix that?
- She can't fix it.
- Right.
In my opinion, it's a chronic condition for Young Ji.
The carrot cake you've all been waiting for is finally here.
I'm sorry about the long wait.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
It's like rice cake.
It tastes like donut.
The bottom tastes like yuzu.
- Yuzu?
- Right?
It's very nice and refreshing.
- Hello.
We have an order.
Okay.
At Table 9, we have 2 ades, 1 carrot cake,
one tteoksagna, one tteokbokki,
1 shrimp burger, and 1 beef burger.
- Okay.
- We can do it.
You're saying that as a habit.
If we don't do this, it's hard to stay sane.
Young Ji, your back looks so sexy right now.
- What?
- Your back looks sexy.
Thank you. How about a kiss?
Goodness.
You're killing my appetite.
Go away.
(Bringing the lost appetite back)
(2 glasses of appetizing pomegranate ade)
Tteokbokki is ready.
One beef burger is ready.
Okay.
- Can I get two ades?
- Yes, here you go.
Gosh, part-timer.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
(Thanks to the part-timer,)
(the appetite-saving dishes are ready in no time.)
You're a lifesaver.
Did you order 1 original tteokbokki at Table 8?
Did you order a shrimp burger combo at Table Seven?
(The finished dishes are quickly served.)
You're here as a family.
- Yes, we are.
- Okay.
Welcome. Hello.
Can someone take their order?
One burger, two tteokbokki, two cakes,
two ades. Is that correct?
- We have an order.
- Okay.
At Table 10, 2 pomegranate ades,
two carrot cakes,
two tteokbokki, and one beef burger.
I heard two tteokbokki.
Two tteokbokki.
(On the verge of being possessed by a bad spirit)
Oh, no.
Yeong Seok... I didn't mean him.
Yu Jin, mashed potatoes...
No, it's not mashed potatoes.
What am I saying?
- These are potato puffs.
- They're in.
- You didn't press the timer.
- You don't need to.
(Trying desperately to pull herself together)
- Do it based on your feeling.
- Darn it.
There are no buns.
(She ends up getting possessed.)
Calm down. It's okay.
- What's going on?
- It's okay.
What's going on?
(What's going on?)
(Scared)
Just serve tteokbokki first. It's okay.
Somebody, please save me.
(One shrimp burger is made.)
(Taking out the tteoksagna after baking it)
One tteoksagna is ready.
Business is booming here.
- Isn't it booming?
- Yes.
We have 5,000 reservations on CatchTable.
People are just keeping an eye out.
They're the same thing.
They keep an eye out to make reservations.
Young Ji, stay strong.
Stay strong.
One original is ready.
(The tteokbokki is complete with everyone cheering her on.)
- My goodness.
- Do you need help?
Could you just put this on the table?
Yes?
Ma'am, could we get some more pickles?
- I'll bring you more pickles.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Isn't it delicious?
- Yes.
(Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin of Yeonhui-dong like the pickle.)
When I'm upstairs,
people keep calling me the owner and ask for more pickles.
They think that I'm the real owner.
- Shall I take it to them?
- Do you mind?
This is...
for Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin of Yeonhui-dong.
- I don't remember the table number.
- That's difficult.
- Are they two people?
- Yes.
- I'll go upstairs and ask...
- They're a couple.
for Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin.
Why don't you take the tteoksagna with you?
- Take these 2.
- For Table 9?
Table Nine and Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin.
- Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin.
- Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin...
- of Yeonhui-dong.
- Okay.
(She's going to meet them now.)
My goodness.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Here's your tteoksagna.
Why are you here?
I'm not sure.
Gosh, it's hot.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
Which one of you is...
Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin of Yeonhui-dong?
(What?)
(At the top of her lungs)
(Which one of you is Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin of Yeonhui-dong?)
Is it you?
- I don't think it's me.
- It's not you?
Are you really not?
- I asked for more pickle.
- Really?
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- You look great together.
(You look great together.)
(KARINA of Yeonhui-dong completed her mission with a hearty laugh.)
(Groaning)
We shouldn't have asked for more.
It feels hot.
(Hyun Bin of Yeonhui-dong gets hot easily.)
Did you find Hyun Bin and Son Ye Jin?
They asked for more pickle,
but they said that they weren't Hyun Bin or Son Ye Jin.
(Satisfied)
- Did you ask that?
- Yes. I didn't know who they were.
(While the part-timer was doing all the work, the head chef...)
(She melted cheese on the patties.)
Director.
Have you ever seen a woman...
making tteokbokki while making burgers?
(It's a rare sight.)
Right?
(This rare woman's tteokbokki is almost ready.)
(The well-cooked beef patties are taken off the grill.)
The rice cakes are ready.
No, I mean the burgers.
Burgers.
(A hearty laugh that's rare)
Goodness.
Burgers are ready. Two of them are ready.
(Two rice cake burgers are ready.)
Young Ji, is the original tteokbokki...
ready yet?
In one minute.
It'd be perfect to serve them together.
One minute and 20 seconds.
- You added 20 seconds.
- Both at the same time.
I want to feel the thrill of serving two at the same time.
- I'll make you feel it.
- We need to serve one beef...
I'll give you that catharsis.
One beef burger needs to go out.
I'll give it to you in three minutes.
Three minutes? Why is the time increasing?
In four minutes.
(Screaming)
(Total chaos)
Do something.
(New customers enter.)
(However...)
(The current situation at Space Rice Cake's hall)
(In the secondary hall)
(And in the main hall)
(The only seats left are tables that haven't been cleared.)
Hello. I'll take your order.
(Unaware of the situation, the servers keep taking orders.)
- One shrimp burger.
- One tteokbokki.
Here you go. Thank you.
(She sends the customers to the 2nd floor.)
Is this it?
Where?
Where should we sit?
- Where shall we sit?
- No.
- The seats...
(The floor manager doesn't notice the situation.)
They have to clear the table.
(Wandering around endlessly)
(Thankfully, they find a server.)
Could we...
Where should we sit?
Where should you sit?
On top of my knees.
- Please wait.
- Thank you.
I'll clear the table. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm very sorry. You made a reservation on CatchTable,
and we neglected to clear the tables.
This is the worst restaurant ever.
(A self-deprecating assessment)
(Glancing)
I'm very busy, but I'll still fix my apron.
Sure. Take your time.
(Rummaging)
Goodness.
(Running away)
It's an apron show.
It's no ordinary task.
(A special show performed out of sheer guilt)
I love you, customers.
I'm sorry about that.
- You're Table One.
- That's right.
- KARINA, we have to clean up.
- Okay.
Clean the tables in the room.
(Cleaning the remaining tables with the part-timer)
- Excuse me.
- Eun Ji, are there customers...
Gosh, hello.
- It's a baby.
- I see. I'm sorry for creating...
a bad environment while you're eating.
- I sincerely apologize once again.
- I'm sorry.
Don't worry. The work must be very hard.
- It's okay.
- It's all right.
I can tell how tired you are on your face.
Are you saying that I have grease...
- on my face?
- No, you're very pretty.
KARINA, sit down and wipe the table.
(Sharing life wisdom with the part-timer)
- Wipe the table while sitting down.
- Shall I?
- It's not an easy job, is it?
- It's not easy.
I've been doing this for days.
What's the date today?
- What? She lost track of time.
- Oh, no.
- Today is the 17th.
- The 17th?
It's the 17th? It's year 2024, right?
(Laughing)
That's a completely different genre.
That's how badly we're living in rice cake inferno every day.
And the head chef is way too obsessed with sales.
Don't you work with her?
The head chef has it even worse downstairs.
- She's struggling more than me.
- She's crying.
- Isn't it chaotic?
She's crying.
We'll get going now.
(They finish cleaning the table with a small talk.)
Take a look around and see if anyone needs anything.
Nothing has been served to Table One.
Go downstairs and see if food is ready for Table One.
- Could you talk like this, KARINA?
- Okay.
Thank you.
Welcome, customers.
This is Space Rice Cake.
(Current time, 7:50pm)
Nice to meet you.
Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
Hello, everyone. Whenever you have time,
feel free to look around the pop-up store.
It's very nice to take photos in here.
One, two, three.
Sir, please open up your chest.
You're a beautiful family.
Please go upstairs.
Feel free to come downstairs and take a look around.
Nothing came out for Table Three.
- Nothing at all?
- No.
What's the order?
- One potato cream tteoksagna, - Mimi.
- one tteokbokki, - Yes.
and one shrimp burger.
A burger? Mimi, fry the shrimp patty first.
I'll be making rice cake buns.
(She finishes it at the right time.)
Tteokbokki is ready.
We have an order.
One soda, one pomegranate ade,
one carrot cake, one tteoksagna,
one tteokbokki, one beef burger,
and one shrimp burger.
It must be the last order of the day. Isn't that right?
It's a jackpot at the end.
Burgers are already out, so take a look.
Yes, burgers are ready.
In this case, I have to use both of my hands.
That's sexy.
Thank you.
- It's hot, so please don't touch.
- Thank you.
If you get hurt, I'll no longer have a reason to work here.
(Now at Table 1)
Yu Jin, carrot cakes... You're doing well.
- Two are ready.
- That's great.
(2 carrot cakes are ready.)
Everything went out for Table One.
- Well done.
- One more carrot cake...
- I think it's for this table.
(However...)
However, there are two.
I'll serve 2 carrot cakes to Table 10.
Eun Ji, could you serve other tables at the same time?
I didn't hear you.
- Two for Table Ten.
- Never mind.
(She discards the order again.)
It's okay
(It's not okay, but she sets off.)
Here are your 2 carrot cakes at Table 10.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
(Table 1 is happily eating, unaware of what's going on.)
The burgers will be coming out a little late...
- Take your time.
- because of the buns.
(Yu Jin is in charge of carrot cake.)
I'll give you some ghee butter.
Here's some ghee butter.
(Young Ji is feeding the rice cake buns.)
(Mimi who has a million things to do)
(Frying up a shrimp patty)
- Mimi.
- Yes?
I'll grill it this time.
No.
Yu Jin... I mean, Young...
(Cutting the rice cakes so perfectly that it leaves you speechless)
Mimi, we're out of shrimp again.
We're out of shrimp again? Here's some more. Come here.
(Restocking the fried food in between)
- Be careful.
- I'll do this first.
(Restocking the fried food in between)
(Even 10 pairs of hands wouldn't be enough right now.)
- KARINA.
- Yes?
Could you bring me some potato puffs from the pantry?
- Potato?
- Potato.
They're called potato puffs. They're like hash browns.
The pronunciation must be unfamiliar.
(However, the pantry is no longer unfamiliar to her.)
(She brings potato puffs for Mimi.)
Thank you so much. Goodness.
The sponge cake is down here.
Thank you.
(Assisting Yu Jin with carrot cake)
Shall I bring another container?
It's just below the table.
- You're so quick.
- Thank you.
KARINA, you work so fast.
- Let's call her back tomorrow.
- I hope she comes back tomorrow.
- Come every day.
- Can you sleep...
at our place tonight?
(An invitation to join their lodging)
Please, KARINA.
- She will never agree to it.
- She's not answering.
(She doesn't say things that she doesn't mean.)
She's brutally honest.
(The last dessert gets ready.)
One carrot cake is ready.
Let the customers eat tteokbokki while it's hot.
Okay.
- Tteokbokki is coming now.
- Okay.
The beef will be ready soon.
- We can serve them together.
- That's great.
Catharsis.
Catharsis. Cathar is my sister.
It's for Table Three.
(The final order is heading out.)
Is there anything you're still waiting on?
- Are you waiting on anything?
- Did you get everything?
- Yes.
- Ade, Coke, and carrot cake.
Ade, Coke, and carrot cake. I apologize.
It's okay.
KARINA, could you help me?
- We sincerely apologize.
- It's okay.
We'll bring them fast. I'm sorry.
Table 8 is missing 1 ade, 1 Coke, and 1 carrot cake.
One ade, one Coke, and one carrot cake.
That's not for us.
We don't know how to make them.
- Did you say carrot cake?
- I'll make the ade.
One ade, one Coke, and one carrot cake.
If they didn't go out, why did someone...
- take off the order?
- I wonder why.
(Why did you take it off?)
(The missing carrot cake remains a mystery to Eun Ji.)
I have no idea.
(The part-timer is making a pomegranate ade.)
We have a highly skilled new recruit.
It's a coming-of-age story.
Thank you.
(Walking awkwardly)
Did you not get your carrot cake yet?
I packed it generously...
as a little apology.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
(Table 1 order)
Is it for them?
(All the orders are sent out.)
Take a quick break, stand up, and look at the sky.
Let's do the new millennium gymnastics starting with the neck.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four,
five, six. Grab a woman next to you.
With the woman in front of you...
(The essence of stretching)
- With her in front of you...
- It's strange with three people.
Playing with fire
(Playing with fire)
- Playing with fire - Playing with fire
- This is terrible.
- It's the last one.
- I don't want to join them.
- Do something - Do something
- Thank you so much for coming.
- Thank you.
Your clothes are getting undone...
- My goodness.
- because you worked so hard.
Yu Ji Min
We look quite shabby, but shall we take...
- a commemorative photo?
- That sounds good.
Where?
(A commemorative photo is a must.)
Hold it right there. One, two, three.
(With their first part-timer)
(Thank you, KARINA.)
- Well done.
- Thank you, KARINA.
- Hurry and go home.
- Go home.
- KARINA.
- Thank you.
I'm leaving. I'll leave without a second thought.
- Walk her out, Yu Jin.
- Well done.
I'm leaving too.
- Let's go. Take care, KARINA.
- Bye.
- I'll miss you.
Goodbye.
(The first part-timer at Space Rice Cake leaves.)
- Take care.
- I'll call you.
Do something.
(The first part-timer at Space Rice Cake leaves.)
Gosh, KARINA.
(One by one, the customers get ready to leave.)
What's his name?
- His name is Ha Ru.
- Ha Ru.
Mother finger, mother finger
Where are you?
(Crying)
I'm sorry.
(Good intentions, bad ending)
Ha Eun liked it.
(Their evening service is over.)
Let's go and clean up.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
(It's time to clean up.)
- We can do it.
Okay.
Mimi, look at this.
They finished everything.
(They finished everything.)
Young Ji, take a photo of this too. They finished all the tteokbokki.
(Posing)
You look so gaunt, but you look even prettier.
(She's more beautiful when she looks gaunt.)
Thank you so much.
Over here too.
- They left some fried food.
- They must've enjoyed it.
(Collecting photos of empty plates)
- Thank you.
- Why are you taking photos...
of empty plates, Young Ji?
It makes me feel so good.
I feel so rewarded.
They cleaned everything on the plates.
There are no leftovers.
I'm so happy.
I'm very happy.
(Caught up in the happiness, she forgot how tired she is.)
They cleaned their plates completely.
Did they clear them out, Young Ji?
They ate them all, Mimi.
(Young Ji kept shouting about how happy she was for a while.)
I'm so happy. Really.
Gosh. It's crazy.
(Current time, 9:07pm)
(After a brief moment of happiness, they're back to reality.)
(Half-asleep)
Today,
- you've done a great job.
- So, thank you.
- Good job.
- Hard work pays off, right?
- Thank you.
- That's right.
Today,
no one was possessed by the evil spirit.
- It even ended on a beautiful note.
- That's right.
- The customers were understanding.
- Yes.
Sales. Let's check today's sales.
- Tell us our sales - Do you know why we check it?
It's not because we want to know...
how we're going to use it later.
- Then?
- If today's sales are bigger
than tomorrow's...
If tomorrow's sales are bigger than yesterday's,
that means we're making progress.
- Yes. I'm proud, indeed.
- That's the meaning of it.
That means we're on the rise.
That we're on an upward trajectory.
So, in conclusion...
Our guru!
- Anyway, we want to check...
- Stop it.
how much progress we've made.
How much growth have we made?
Is it okay to still grow when I'm 35?
- You look like you're 15...
- Yes.
- with a youthful face.
- Thanks.
- How much?
- How much is it?
Did it go up or down?
- I'm going to grow.
- Is it an all-time high?
- Is it the highest ever?
- It's the highest.
In total, what you made today...
- is 1,082.8 dollars.
- And 80 dollars.
I thought it was 1,800 dollars.
- It's over 1,000 dollars!
- It's over 1,000 dollars.
- It's the first time ever.
- It's a first for us.
Why are you killing the mood?
- Why are you so ambitious?
- What's with you?
- How much more do you want?
- Let's enjoy the moment together.
Why are you so ambitious in a fake way?
(Today's growth)
(16 beef burgers, 18 shrimp burgers, 18 original tteokbokki,)
(14 tteoksagna, 17 mint carrot cake, 14 ades, 16 ade options, 5 sodas)
(Total sales: 1,082.8 dollars)
(It's an all-time high.)
(Breaking news! They reached 1,000 dollars!)
- Is that our all-time high?
- Is there a real and a fake way?
Basically, each team ordered...
- about 49.22 dollars.
- That's crazy.
They ordered one of everything on the menu.
Tomorrow,
- we're adding the pizza.
- Yes.
We'll boldly remove tteoksagna from the menu.
And we'll add the pizza instead.
"Pizza."
But what is the thing I can't let go of?
(Ghost pepper)
(Ghost pepper pizza)
(It's a challenge)
(Margherita)
(Ghost pepper)
We're going for it.
(New dish: Ghost pepper pizza)
(On the sticky rice cake dough,)
(generous amount of a spicy sauce...)
(and cheese are added to make this pizza.)
- I can't let it go.
- Then give me a name.
Its name and price.
Ghost...
- pepper.
- Okay.
- Ghost pepper pizza.
- Ghost pepper.
- That's it.
- In 3, 2, 1,
- ghost pepper pizza.
- Ghost pepper pizza.
I want to hear Mi Hyun's version.
Ghost pepper.
(Chef Mimi will focus on cooking.)
(It's time to add it to the menu!)
- We'll remove the tteoksagna.
- Remove it for now.
Ghost pepper...
- pizza.
- But it hurts...
- to delete it from the menu.
- I'll do it.
I can't delete it.
Is there a hide button?
Is there a "hide the dish" option?
I'll do it.
(Manage your menu)
(Just like that, tteoksagna fade into history.)
Give it to me, Eun Ji.
We sold lots of tteoksagna today, didn't we?
- We did.
- Yes.
It's very tasty and popular,
but since we need to focus,
we'll say goodbye to it for a while.
It's time to say goodbye. It was from Goheung.
- Exactly. We made plenty of it.
- Let it go.
Now, a description of the dish.
Spicy.
- Ghost pepper pizza.
- Delicious.
Shape your smile, let your fortune rise.
Knead away your frowns.
- Stretch your back.
- Shape your smile.
- Knead away your frowns.
- How about 22 dollars?
- Yes, 22 dollars.
- It's cute.
- It's much better.
Ghost pepper pizza?
- It's 22 dollars.
- You're good.
- Good.
I added it to the menu.
(A new dish has been added to the menu!)
(Ghost pepper pizza)
(A spicy handmade pizza made with tasty sticky rice cake dough)
- Make the part-timer come sooner.
- Yes.
We'll try to tell them..
- to come as early as possible.
- But who is it?
- I want CORTIS.
- Who is it?
- Their joints are still healthy.
- Tomorrow...
- Give us a hint.
- Nam...
- Eun Ji is close to them.
It's Yang Bae Cha.
- Yu Jin might be close to them.
- Or the CEO in Busan.
- Do you think I'm close to them?
- Yes.
Is there a mutual friend...
between you and me?
Eun Ji definitely knows the person.
- You know that person.
- Yes.
Anyway,
- one with strong joints, please.
- Yes.
I think that person is very healthy.
- Then it's Moon Sang Hoon.
- Seo Jang Hoon?
- No. It's Shownu.
- Moon Sang Hoon.
- You're just saying...
- No.
someone you'd love to come.
- It's not someone you like.
- You're making a wish.
Don't ask Taec Yeon to come.
Are you calling Ok Taec Yeon? He's married.
Okay. We made 1,080 dollars today.
Let's aim for 1,500 dollars tomorrow.
Let's go!
- Go!
- It's my first time...
- Honesty
Two, three.
- Go!
- It's my first time...
running a business.
- Honesty, humility, ahk.
- Humility, ahk.
Let's go.
(Current time, 9:37pm)
Protect Yu Jin.
I can't see because it's dark.
Be careful. Are you okay?
(After a labour-intensive day,)
Thank you.
- Go.
- Why isn't it working?
(they can't help but yawn.)
- I just need to follow that car.
- Yes.
Did you forget them?
I left the kitchen shoes here.
I see. You left them here.
Let's do this.
Let's go.
So, the part-timer tomorrow.
- Who's coming?
- Who is it?
Can you just ask a few of your friends to come?
My friends are Yoo Seung Ho and BIBI.
KARINA was a great help today.
- Yes.
- Right.
She did all the hard work.
- Yes.
- You're right.
- And she came straight from work.
- Right.
- Seriously.
- It must've been so tough.
(Shout-out to KARINA!)
- By the way, today was...
- Wasn't it so hard?
- It was exhausting.
- I lost it before I knew it.
- You were possessed.
- For a moment.
(Hectic 1st day of business)
I'm exhausted.
We only have a few days left. About three days.
(Those 3 days will feel like 3 years.)
It's much better to be exhausted from losing energy...
while having fun together.
This is not just about having fun.
- There is a lot to take care of.
- Yes.
That's what makes it harder.
Even when I'm taking a short break, I'm still thinking...
- about what to do next.
- Yes.
- We have to find things to do.
We can't take a break during the break.
- A lot is on my mind.
- Yes.
We're doing it because we're responsible.
- That's right.
(Thinking about the business on their way home)
(A lifesaver is waiting for these drained souls.)
Hello. Let's clean up.
Hello.
Yes, I'm here.
Please vacuum this place.
(Yes, ma'am.)
(Reaching)
- It avoids it very well.
- It avoids it.
- Gosh.
It's turning well, navigating around the obstacles.
Go that way.
- Go that way.
- That way.
It's going that way.
(Let's check.)
- It's hot.
- It's sanitized with hot water.
Gosh. It's navigating around the couch legs.
- It reaches the end.
- It's very smart.
- It cleans the corners well.
- Yes.
(Thanks to it, they finished cleaning with ease.)
Go back to the dock.
Okay. Returning to the charging dock.
(Good job.)
Awesome.
It's moving backward.
- It doesn't smell bad. I love it.
- It's moonwalking.
- Bye.
- Good job.
(They finished cleaning up without lifting a finger.)
(A spotless night comes to an end.)
(It's clear today.)
(It's a perfect day for customers to come.)
(Young Ji and Yu Jin's room)
Your Majesty.
We'll leave in 20 minutes.
(She wakes the sleepy king.)
(They're looking fancy in new uniforms.)
You do look like those people.
The ones who work at fast-food chains.
(The dress code for the service team is navy.)
- Okay. I'll handle it myself.
- Yu Jin is so cute.
(The kitchen team is wearing matching ringer t-shirts.)
I just need to put on the lipstick.
- Do you want some thrill?
- Yes.
(All eyes are on her.)
You're really good at it.
Hey. You look like someone who grills patties really well.
(A master of patties, indeed.)
It's annoying to hear that I'd flip patties well.
(Laughing)
(The master of patties is ready to go to work.)
Will there be fewer reservations since it's Monday?
I don't think so.
Yesterday, the bookings on CatchTable for both days...
- Is it all full?
- were done.
(Disappointed)
(It won't be easy today again.)
I'm hungry.
- Me too.
- I'm hungry.
- I'm starving.
- We can eat...
only after learning about the dough.
Should we order deliveries from time to time?
- For us?
- Let's order deliveries...
- for lunch.
- Yes.
We can use delivery apps.
Let's order yogurt ice cream.
- Yogurt ice cream.
- That's...
That's not a meal.
- Isn't it delicious?
- It's not a meal.
Ice cream.
At a gimbap place near here,
I want to have kimchi fried rice and...
pork cutlet, and hold a snack party.
Okay. I want to work after just having some gimbap.
I don't want gimbap. We had it yesterday, Boss.
How about fried tofu pockets?
- Sounds good.
- Sounds great.
Let's have fried tofu pockets with cup noodles.
- Good.
- That's a great idea.
Let's eat quickly and learn or learn first, then eat.
Does that cafe have a regular day off?
Gosh. We don't have a day off.
What?
(Jealous)
(The streets look emptier today.)
(Yawning)
(Tired)
No yawning today.
- But we can't hold it.
- At least don't make a sound...
- because it's contagious.
- Okay.
When someone yawns,
- I also yawn right away.
- Right.
It's contagious.
- See?
- Yawns are contagious.
She's doing it again.
(Laughing)
(You have to laugh it off even when you don't want to.)
We're here.
(That's the mindset of a pro.)
(They overcome the Monday blues and yawns...)
I can't tell the distance up front.
(to come to work for the 2nd day in Seoul!)
You're fine on the side.
- Thank you.
- Thanks for driving.
Okay. Be careful.
I want it.
(After parking nicely and diagonally...)
Let's park it again after the opening.
- Rice cake is here.
- Gosh. It's here.
(The rice cakes welcome them like always.)
- Hello. To the pantry?
- Good morning.
(They enter with the rice cakes.)
Gosh. I can't do this. Really.
(She's wiped out after working 2 days at the 2nd branch.)
Why did you write a horse on the towel today?
- I'm going to run like a horse.
- Okay.
Also, I was born in the Year of the Horse.
- Thanks.
(Wearing today's resolution)
Good morning, Ye Seul.
(Hello, everyone.)
(Bowing)
(The older ones are a mess too.)
- The uniform is...
- Yes.
- You're cute today.
- You didn't have to.
Yes. It's okay.
Just during the business hours.
Wait. Doesn't Yu Jin have that vibe today?
The pretty ones back in the days...
- Right.
- got scouted while working...
- at a fast-food chain.
- She's pretty.
- Goodness.
We're having a light breakfast with fried tofu pockets...
- And cup noodles.
- and cup noodles.
- Yes.
- During mealtime.
I'll order the fried tofu pockets on the delivery app.
- Use the HQ's card, Eun Ji.
- Okay.
How about these fried tofu pockets?
- They look good.
- Traditional fried tofu pockets.
The pollack roe mayo and salmon rice balls look good.
I'll add them.
- Tuna and mayo.
- Pollack roe mayo...
- is so tasty.
- I'll add it.
Let's have a bite of the one with pickled chillies.
I'll have one bomb rice ball.
(Their order list is loaded as they're using the HQ's card.)
The bomb rice ball.
- Should we get royal milk tea?
- We can make...
- Or peach juice?
- a pomegranate ade.
- We'll eat anything that's there.
- Sure. The pomegranate ade.
We want everything. I understand.
(They finished ordering drinks too.)
Okay.
Now, until the food comes,
let's make the dough.
(What she means is...)
What's important today anyway?
- Right. We're learning the new one.
- We learn it today.
- It's pizza.
- Pizza.
- Pizza?
- Burgers and pizza.
- I knew it.
- There's room for pizza.
- Pizza?
(Another new dish at the 2nd branch)
(Ghost pepper pizza)
(The sticky rice cake dough that's chewy...)
(and flaming hot sauce are the kick to the recipe.)
We should make the dough first, right?
- Yes.
- Pizza and pasta.
As for the dough,
- you have sticky rice cake, right?
- Yes.
Let's spread it out.
That's cute.
This pizza will taste great as it's made with sticky rice cake.
Roll it out.
(Rolling it out against its stickiness)
(When it shapes like a pizza dough...)
- That's good enough.
- Yes. That's good.
- Goodness.
- You're good.
We'll cook it slowly over low heat.
It has to be crispy,
so we have to cook it slowly for a long time.
- Don't let it burn.
- Okay.
(When it's nice and golden...)
I'm sorry.
- Very good.
Very good.
(The golden, puffed-up dough is ready.)
Now, we'll put a spicy sauce on it.
Okay. It's tomato puree.
- Tomato puree.
- We'll add five cups.
One cup of minced garlic.
- Then add a cup of Buldak sauce.
- Okay.
Can I add some flavours of my own?
- Ghost peppers?
- Yes.
(The sauce for the ghost pepper pizza)
I added it.
(Mix tomato puree, minced garlic, Buldak sauce, salt, pepper, sugar,)
(and ghost pepper powder to make the spicy sauce.)
Perfect.
- We'll add the sauce.
- It's a cute pizza.
Mushroom soup?
- We'll leave the crust part.
- Okay.
We need a handle to grab on.
- It's visually stunning.
- Yes.
- Please add lots of mozzarella.
- Got it.
- Chorizo slices.
- What's chorizo?
- Right.
Next, mushrooms.
- Mushrooms.
How many minutes?
- Eight minutes.
- Great.
- Basil smells good.
- It smells fantastic.
Stop. No, add some more.
- Okay.
- It's tasty.
- Is it good?
- Pizza's ready.
- Are we done with the pizza?
- Yes, we are.
I served it with honey.
(Getting ready for the day following the recipe they learned)
I'll go get the dough.
Let's wash our hands.
(Hygiene first before prep.)
We'll chant first.
- Honesty, humility, - Humility,
- ahk.
- Yu Jin didn't chant.
- I did say, "ahk."
(Hurriedly)
How much should one lump...
of the dough weigh?
- It has to be 230g.
- Is it 230g?
(Dividing the sticky rice cake into 230-g portions)
How much should it weigh?
It should be 230g.
(They said it 10 seconds ago.)
- How many times did I ask?
- You're asking the same question.
I heard it, but I couldn't remember.
It goes through my head like this.
It's because it's hectic.
- It's 230g.
(Will everything be okay today when they're clumsy already?)
Wasn't it done already?
- How much is 230g?
- It's here.
I think it's this much.
Please sprinkle some on mine too.
- It's 229g.
- It's about this much.
- It's the exact amount.
- Go for it, Yu Jin.
- I think it's more than 230g.
- Here I come.
- Go for it.
How much does it weigh?
It's 226g.
Yu Jin, remember how it felt in your hand.
It's too sticky. What should I do?
- It's 297g.
- Hey.
- It's a pass.
- Is this good enough?
- Yes. It's a pass.
- Okay.
(They're doing a sensory play.)
What should we do with the container, Yu Jin? Look.
- You and I are...
- We should only bake it.
I'll try it again.
Why can't you do it when you're the kitchen team?
- Why do you find it so hard?
- Please take it back.
Please hold on. Put your hands over there.
Should I get rid of this, Mimi?
Do it at once.
You have to keep putting the flour on your hands.
We set them like this...
- and put them in the oven.
- That's right.
- Gosh. You're the dough queen.
- It's hot.
She's amazing.
(The head chef cooks the dough.)
She got it. Young Ji got the hang of it.
- I want it to be round.
- Me too. Let's roll it out.
- But this is...
- But when we put it...
on here like this, it'll be okay.
Gosh. You're doing great, Mimi. It's nice and even.
- Is it okay?
- It's great. It's smooth.
- How did you make it so round?
- I think...
I rolled it vertically first.
Then I flipped it and rolled it horizontally.
Then I made the shape.
(It's easier said than done.)
(The head chef is trying to flip it.)
(But the dough won't come off the pan.)
Push it forward and flip it.
(Her second attempt)
(She finally pulls it off!)
- Where do I put it?
- Nice.
(Where do I put it?)
- Place another one, please.
- You do look...
- like a real Italian chef.
- Yes.
- No.
- The measuring queen.
(After mixing the spicy-looking sauce well,)
How does this look, Young Ji?
(it's time for a mid-way check.)
- It's perfect.
- Is it?
Try it, Yu Jin.
It's not spicy at all.
Isn't it a mushroom pizza?
Shall we bake it?
- Bake it.
- Bake it, please.
(They bake it nice and hot.)
- I want lots of cheese.
- Yes.
- The bottom is...
- It's fine.
(They sprinkle it with cheese to finish.)
Please give it a try.
(The ghost pepper pizza is ready.)
Dip it in honey. We need to serve it with honey, everyone.
- Yes.
- That's right.
(Trying it)
How is it?
- Is it good?
- She likes it.
- Is it good, Eun Ji?
- This is it.
Ghost pepper tastes good, doesn't it?
The ghost pepper tastes incredible.
(The head chef tries it too.)
How is it?
(The sous chef takes a bite too.)
I'll take it.
Is it good?
I told you it was good.
It tastes like the ghost pepper I know.
(Everyone loves how deliciously spicy it is.)
- It's tasty.
- Ghost pepper's better than Buldak.
Dipping it in honey...
- makes it even better.
- It tastes better.
Let's do a limited quantity of ten pizzas.
- Let's do 10.
- Let's make 10.
Great idea.
I'm going to make a Goheung sea margarita.
(Last night)
- Then...
- Should we change it?
should we add a refreshing drink...
- to the pizza?
- Sounds good.
Should I make it with a shaker?
- A non-alcoholic one.
- Sounds great.
I'll try making some stuff tomorrow.
Try them tomorrow.
(It's clear and blue like the sea of Goheung.)
(It's sweet, sour, and refreshing.)
(New drink: Non-alcoholic Goheung sea margarita)
(Setting the cocktail shaker)
I've never used it before.
Two tablespoons of peach juice.
I love grapefruit juice.
(Grapefruit juice)
I'm going to recreate the sea of Goheung.
Nice.
(Sparkling water)
Two tablespoons of sparkling water.
(Ice)
- Yu Jin.
- Yes?
Do you want me to cheer you up?
Yes, please.
Hold on.
- You and I - And I
- It's more than "Like"
(L, O, and yes)
(You and I, it's more than "Like")
(Super excited)
(A tribute to Yu Jin who's tired)
- You look like a happy seal.
- Thanks.
(Playing the next song, riding the momentum)
(This one is for the second eldest sister.)
Mimi, look at me while working on it.
(My heart fluttered a little)
No! Goodness.
Gosh. I'm sorry.
(Starting the next song with the same spirit)
(This time, it's a performance for the second sister.)
Watch as you're doing that, Mimi.
I was a little flustered
I'm sorry.
(The show was cut short.)
- I'm sorry.
- Goodness.
Goodness.
- We've become happy.
- Goodness.
It was like the Waterbomb Festival.
- It was nice.
- I'm not used to...
I'll do it. Your hands are meant to eat food.
(I spilled it a little.)
This is funny.
They do things like this at cocktail bars.
Like this. They rim the glass with lemon juice...
and sugar.
We can add a garnish.
(Perching lemon on the edge of the glass)
(It's time to pour the cocktail from the shaker.)
Goodness. That looks pretty.
- It looks so pretty.
- Does it look okay?
- It feels like I'm at a resort.
- It looks really pretty.
- Does it look like a pretty sea?
- Totally.
- It looks like a pretty sea.
(The head chef tastes first.)
(She approves.)
Is it okay?
(The dessert master also takes a sip.)
You definitely are an all-rounder.
It felt like a real evaluation. It was like "Culinary Class Wars."
Thank you for the compliment.
(A new menu item is ready!)
- Let's eat something.
- Okay.
Let's eat quickly.
- Have some.
- Thank you for the meal.
Enjoy.
- Is it ready?
- Enjoy.
(Eating)
It's like eating ramyeon...
- at a ski resort.
- Right.
I think we should just assume...
it'll be a bit chaotic in the morning.
The kitchen is always a little chaotic.
Think about what we have to prepare.
(She's talking about work already.)
- Eun Ji, the pomegranate ade...
- Yes, chef.
You're only making the pomegranate ade and margarita, right?
Yu Jin...
- is on the carrot cake...
- I'm on pomegranate ade...
- and carrot cake.
- Yes.
- Mimi will prepare pizza here.
I just need to make pizza and fritters.
I'll make tteokbokki, burgers, and fritters.
Please take good care of the hall with our precious customers.
- Our guardian angels.
- Yes, chef.
But things don't go as expected in restaurants.
- Right. Nothing goes as planned.
- Let's prepare as much as we can.
- Yes.
- Right.
(20 minutes before opening)
- I feel like throwing up.
- Right.
We have to hurry.
The torture began again.
(They have no choice but to do it.)
Right.
We can put it down.
(She sets the carrot cakes for faster serving.)
(They're ready to open!)
I'm baking the bread. I'm almost done.
I think we need a new part-timer today.
The part-timer needs to come quickly.
We're going to make...
good use of the part-timer.
(Current time, 11:30am)
(Enjoying the last moment of calm before opening)
Opening the sign
We're open. Welcome!
Thank you for visiting.
(They're open for lunch now.)
Thank you for your service.
(Good luck today.)
(Starting Day Two with a clean workspace)
We'll have pizza here.
- This will be the burger tray.
- Okay.
(The first customers arrive.)
We love you to the space.
Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
I'm glad you came today.
You have a new pizza item.
- We studied in advance.
- Thank you so much.
Please take your time to order.
(The kitchen is nervous even before the first order.)
Please head upstairs.
Please help yourselves to dishes and utensils. Take this.
One beef burger, one shrimp burger, one original tteokbokki,
one pizza, one carrot cake, one margarita, and one soda.
(The first customers order the entire menu.)
That's Table One.
Margarita, as in the pizza?
It's the pizza...
- Margarita isn't pizza.
- Okay.
(I'm ghost pepper pizza.)
(I'm margarita.)
(Both new menu items have been ordered!)
Welcome.
Under whose name did you make the reservation?
- Are you here alone?
- Yes.
Okay. Nice to meet you.
- A beef burger and a carrot cake.
- Okay.
(Luckily, it's just 1 customer, so the order is simple.)
(She prepares the soda before she gets confused.)
I know you're busy, but please take a look at this.
This is the order it will be served.
- First, second, third.
- Okay.
(Young Ji places the beef patty on the grill...)
(and checks the tteokbokki.)
Are the fritters done, Mi Hyun?
They're done.
There's no need to rush.
(She hands them to the head chef.)
Thank you.
Can the original tteokbokki...
- be served first?
- Sure.
If it gets too tough in the kitchen, you can ask Yu Jin for help.
Okay.
- I'll work on the pizza.
- Okay.
(Since it's a new menu item, she carefully reads the recipe.)
(Yu Jin is in charge of pizza today.)
(She spreads the spicy sauce evenly,)
(sprinkles some mozzarella cheese,)
(adds chorizo,)
(adds button mushroom,)
(and bakes it in the oven.)
(While the pizza bakes,)
(Eun Ji is preparing another new menu item.)
(She adds the ingredients.)
(Shaking)
(Role satisfaction: 116 percent)
(Rimming the glass with lemon juice)
(Dipping it in sugar)
(She pours it into a glass.)
(Goheung sea margarita is ready.)
(Yu Jin gets out the cakes she prepared earlier...)
(and completes them with cute carrot cakes.)
It's 1, 2, and 3 from the left, right?
That's right.
It's too early for the carrot cake, but it's out first.
(The dessert orders are moving too fast.)
- Can the tteokbokki be served?
- Yes.
The shrimp burger will be ready soon.
(The tteokbokki is ready first.)
(Eun Ji is about to serve it.)
(Spilling)
Goodness. My margarita.
- What's wrong with you?
- Margarita?
- Okay.
- The margarita became like this.
Serving margaritas up the stairs will be hard.
(Worrying about the margaritas)
(Carrot cake for Table 1, carrot cake for Table 2)
How am I going to take the margarita up the stairs?
- It won't be easy.
- What should I do with it?
I should take it separately.
(She separates the margarita.)
It's not easy.
Isn't there a dumbwaiter for dishes?
(She serves the dishes without the margarita first.)
Young Ji's original tteokbokki is here.
Thank you.
I'll serve the cute carrot cake as well.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Did we order 2 carrot cakes?
- I ordered 1.
Did you order one carrot cake?
- Yes.
- Then I'll take one back.
Thank you for the honest confession.
(Eun Ji forgot that the carrot cake was for Table 2.)
(That's mine.)
(Table 2 carrot cake is put aside.)
(She's happily checking things off.)
(Eun Ji is only worried about the margarita.)
What am I going to do with the margarita?
Should we take margarita off the menu?
It's really hard to serve this.
- I should just make 2 trips.
- Yes. Make 2 trips.
(Round 1: serving burgers)
I'm worried it might spill.
The margarita for the customers...
(She serves it with extreme caution.)
These are my tears.
Goodness.
- Thank you.
- Today might be tough.
(She serves the margarita after a struggle.)
- Thank you.
I think we'll have to make...
a margarita zone in the second-floor pantry.
If there's a margarita zone in the second-floor pantry,
I might become a very hot bartender.
I'll set up a margarita zone in the second-floor pantry.
(A new margarita station)
(Look forward to Bartender Eun who'll work with more ease.)
(Young Ji is making beef burgers.)
Nice. That's cool.
Thank you.
(She takes out the nicely cooked patties.)
(Chef Mimi slices the rice cake bun.)
(Spreading basil mayonnaise sauce)
(Placing the patty on the rice cake bun)
(Placing arugula and tomatoes)
(Finishing off with a Torong pick)
(The sous chef plates the fritters...)
(and the sauce.)
- One beef burger is ready.
- Okay.
(Yu Jin carefully looks at the order ticket.)
(The carrot cake for Table 2 has been sitting there.)
(She moves the main dish and leaves the area.)
(She places it in the tray for Table 2...)
(and checks again.)
(The carrot cake miraculously returned to its place.)
Your order is ready.
Here you go.
(It's a relief.)
(The pizza was baked for 8 minutes in the oven.)
(It came out perfectly golden.)
(She adds the toppings like she learned.)
(Grating pecorino cheese)
(She's about to slice the pizza.)
I should have sliced it first, right?
(Slicing through the leaf)
(With no other choice, she finishes cutting it.)
(Rearranging the basil at the end)
(The first pizza came out all right.)
Goodness.
(She runs into Eun Ji on her way up.)
- This is for Table One.
- Thank you.
(She naturally hands it to her.)
This is quite hot.
(Table 1)
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
(Yu Jin rushes downstairs.)
(She marks the order ticket to avoid confusion.)
It's spicy.
- Is it very spicy?
- It's very spicy.
- Really?
It gets better after some time.
It gets really spicy when you keep eating it.
It's spicy.
(Opinions are divided on how spicy it is.)
- It's good.
- Right.
(The new menu item is getting good reviews.)
(Taking a sip of the margarita)
I don't know what flavour it is.
- But it's good.
- It's good?
- Powerade...
- It's sweet.
It's very sticky.
- It's very sticky.
- Yes.
These are my tears.
(We're sorry about that.)
Hello. Welcome.
Hello.
A table for four, right?
It's beef hamburger combo...
and shrimp hamburger combo...
and this is tteokbokki.
- Do you know what it is?
- Yes.
And this one is pizza which is very hot.
How about the drinks?
Do these two already have drinks?
Yes, you already have one Coke for each one.
(Amazing)
An Yu Genius.
(The reliable golden youngest)
Okay.
We have an order.
One carrot cake, one pizza,
one tteokbokki, one shrimp burger, and one beef burger.
- Okay.
(Dissolving the tteokbokki sauce)
(Spreading the pizza sauce)
(Cutting the rice cake bun)
(They all start cooking in perfect sync.)
(They started...)
(The sound of cutting a rice cake bun)
(The sound of spreading pizza sauce)
(Only silence fills the kitchen.)
(This is a variety show, but no one is speaking.)
It's so tough.
(Laughing)
Plump shrimp popping in!
Enjoy the meal. I love you.
Thank you.
(Singing)
Hello.
Enjoy.
Should I take a picture of you?
- Sure.
- Come this way.
- Where...
- We came from Taiwan.
You're from Taiwan?
I really love pineapple cakes.
- Taiwan...
- Pineapple cakes.
Pineapple cakes.
One, two, three.
Try this place too. It looks pretty in the pictures.
Pineapple cakes!
(Eun Ji's spirit of hospitality)
- The fritters.
- Okay.
They're ready, right?
Nice.
Here's your order.
(Food gets served the moment they sit down.)
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
(Table 4: ghost pepper pizza, shrimp burger set, beef burger set)
Nice, Young Ji.
- Thank you.
- It's crazy.
(The kitchen gets a chance to relax.)
The oven master.
(Having fun)
I moved the margarita zone to the second floor.
Please recommend it to the customers.
- Okay.
- Tell them it's a new menu item.
(A car pulls up to the restaurant.)
Goodness.
It's dazzling.
All the characters are here.
Space Rice Cake?
(The next customer reacts well.)
(She carefully enters.)
(Yang Hee Eun visited Space Rice Cake.)
We just need to finish this.
Beef burger is out.
(So how did this happen?)
(It was on the bus ride back from Goheung.)
- I get why Yang Hee Eun said this.
- What?
"I'm curious about Young Ji's middle and high school years."
It would be nice if she came to eat.
- Right. It would be nice.
- Right.
Should we call Yang Hee Eun and ask her to help us?
I also want Yang Hee Eun to come.
(They never stopped thinking about Hee Eun.)
You can make one now.
(They film a video message right away.)
- Hello.
We're "Earth..."
- "Arcade."
The production crew suddenly told us...
to open a second location in Seoul,
so we had to rush to open a second location.
So we rushed back to Seoul.
Make sure to visit if you have time!
You have to!
(That's how they invited the special guest.)
Goodness!
- Goodness!
- Hello!
(Goodness)
(Hello)
Hee Eun!
Hey.
- Hee Eun.
- What are you doing? Hello.
(Hello)
- Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
You must have been busy.
No way. This voice...
(The head chef drops everything to go greet her.)
Hee Eun.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Young Ji is tired right now.
Why? Because you couldn't sleep?
Yes. I'm doing my best in there.
- Hello.
(Ppippi also greets her.)
(While the kitchen team continues with the burger...)
- Take a look around here.
- Sure.
- We were working in Goheung...
- Right.
at the first location of Space Rice Cake.
They suddenly said we should open a second one in Seoul.
- Who?
- The production crew.
- Hee Eun.
- What is this place?
- It's a mortar for pounding.
- To make rice cakes?
Yes. It's for pounding the rice cakes.
Pounding rice cakes. It looks so pretty.
- It's so pretty.
- Let me take a picture of you.
Sure.
It's my first time being in such a space.
Goodness.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
- Three.
(Please take a good picture of me.)
- It looks great.
- Nice.
I'll serve the other customers their order.
Okay. This place is so beautiful.
(Eun Ji takes Table 4 order.)
Table Four.
(Hee Eun goes upstairs to look around.)
It looks so pretty.
Does it look all right?
- Yes, the spaces are amazing.
- Right.
There's a second floor.
It's really cool. It's an old house.
- This place?
- They're all houses.
- That looks delicious.
- I see.
Here's your table.
Nice.
(She takes a seat.)
Margarita. Zesty pomegranate ade.
It's a homemade burger.
- But it's a rice cake bun.
- Rice cake.
- I'll get a shrimp burger.
- You'll get a shrimp burger.
- Yes.
- Okay. Shrimp.
- One tteokbokki as well.
- And one pomegranate ade.
- One pomegranate ade.
- Okay. Please wait a moment.
- Okay.
Shrimp burger, tteokbokki, pomegranate ade.
(She goes down repeating the order and runs into...)
There's a self utensil station upstairs.
- You can place this on your table.
- Okay.
Thank you.
There's a self utensil station upstairs.
You can place this on your table.
One tteokbokki, one pomegranate ade, and one shrimp burger.
One beef burger, one tteokbokki, one pizza, one carrot cake,
and one non-alcoholic margarita.
Yes.
Here's an order.
One ade, one carrot cake,
one tteokbokki, and one beef burger.
(Coming up next)
(Let's do our work!)
(Just thinking about opening has them worried.)
(Feeling conflicted)
(Then came...)
(a valuable employee!)
(Hello)
- Goodness!
- Hello.
(Queen Gabee, the part-timer for Day 2)
(Goodness! I'm nervous! This is crazy!)
(Despite the nerves, she has remarkable showmanship.)
(It can be a little spicy.)
(Great service with helpful explanations)
(Adapting with ease with plenty of composure)
(The vibe up there feels really good right now.)
(She's even thoughtful enough to ease the kitchen team's worries.)
(Hello)
(A capable new hire they can trust)
(The employees are very satisfied.)
(The all-round part-timer...)
(who's now part of Space Rice Cake.)
(This is fun...)
(so far.)
- So far.
(Things have been going well so far at the Space Rice Cake.)
One, two, three, four...
(Cracks have started to form.)
It's okay.
(Mi Hyun!)
(What did they say?)
(They're all in shock.)
(The head chef steps in to resolve the issue.)
(We’ll work hard to make Space Rice Cake...)
(even more dedicated to serving you.)
(We're truly sorry.)
(Do you think I can't do it?)
(Do you think I can't get through this?)
(Do you think I'll fail?)
(Will they be able to safely get through next week?)
(Space Rice Cake)